{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5409","name":"PizzaPlex","address":"4454 W Vernor","zipcode":"48214","owner":"Andrew McUsic","licenseNumber":"220965","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.09626,42.32017","geojson":{"id":"5409","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.096255739,42.320171505]},"properties":{"name":"PizzaPlex","owner":"Andrew McUsic","address":"4454 W Vernor","zipcode":"48214","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"220965","establishmentid":"5409","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/17/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5387","name":"Flowers of Vietnam","address":"4430 W Vernor","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"470","name":"Neveria La Michoacana","address":"4336 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"794","name":"Armando's Mexican Restaurant","address":"4242 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5402","name":"Antojitos Los Tres Hermanos","address":"4627 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3711","name":"Little Caesar's #166","address":"4635 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"979","name":"Clippert Academy","address":"1981 McKinstry St","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1613","name":"Chicago's Pizza","address":"4650 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1455","name":"V. L. Bar","address":"4654 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51622804","name":"Mutiny Bar ","address":"4654 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51622884","name":"China House","address":"1650 Lansing St","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50391","inspectionDate":"2020-01-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"VENT PANEL","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"48118","inspectionDate":"2019-06-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"Self-closing device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"44178","inspectionDate":"2018-11-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"In the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor drain(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"40131","inspectionDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-701.11","violationDescription":"(A) A FOOD that is unsafe, ADULTERATED, or not honestly presented as specified under § 3-101.11 shall be discarded or reconditioned according to an APPROVED procedure. (P)   \r\n(B) FOOD that is not from an APPROVED source as specified under \r\n§§ 3-201.11 - .17 shall be discarded. (P)   \r\n(C) READY-TO-EAT FOOD that may have been contaminated by an EMPLOYEE who has been RESTRICTED or EXCLUDED as specified under § 2-201.12 shall be discarded. (P) \r\n(D) FOOD that is contaminated by FOOD EMPLOYEES, CONSUMERS, or other PERSONS through contact with their hands, bodily discharges, such as nasal or oral discharges, or other means shall be discarded. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Contaminated food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not discarded","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"39166","inspectionDate":"2017-07-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-102.11","violationDescription":"(A) The outdoor walking and driving areas shall be surfaced with concrete, asphalt, or gravel or other materials that have been effectively treated to minimize dust, facilitate maintenance, and prevent muddy conditions.\r\n(B) Exterior surfaces of buildings and mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS shall be of weather-resistant materials and shall comply with LAW.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outdoor walking and driving surface","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Allows for muddy conditions","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide cement, asphalt, or gravel treated to prevent dust."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Brick(s)/cement block(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable, light in color."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Brick(s)/cement block(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to be","subProblem":"Nonabsorbent","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable, light in color."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Brick(s)/cement block(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"Wall(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable, light in color."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Brick(s)/cement block(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to be","subProblem":"Nonabsorbent","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable, light in color."},{"violationCode":"6-201.17","violationDescription":"(A) Except as otherwise allowed by law, attachments to walls and ceilings such as light fixtures, mechanical room ventilation system components, vent covers, wall mounted fans, decorative items, and other attachments shall be EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) In a CONSUMER area, wall and ceiling surfaces and decorative items and attachments that are provided for ambiance need not meet this requirement if they are kept clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall attachment(s)","subItem":"ventilation system components","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.16","violationDescription":"Perimeter walls and roofs of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall effectively protect the establishment from the weather and the entry of insects, rodents, and other animals.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exterior perimeter","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not protect from weather","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair."},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"50 foot candles","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"and the Storage room","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"light shield(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In service area","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not durable","subProblem":"Designed","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be durable under normal use."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall material(s)","subItem":"for repair","problemDescription":"Not durable","subProblem":"Designed To retain characteristic qualities under normal use conditions","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be durable under normal use."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"Gaps greater than 1/16 of an inch","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Bare wood","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace/seal to be smooth, durable, non-absorbent, and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-08-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5409"}}